<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
<model_name>WNCE2001</model_name>
<lang>Eng</lang>
<lang_ver>1.0.0.1</lang_ver>
<lang_date>2010-03-02</lang_date>
<LUP001>Select Language</LUP001>
<LUP002>English Deutsch Français Italiano</LUP002>
<LUP003>English German French Italian</LUP003>
<LUP004>Apply</LUP004>
<LUP005>WPS</LUP005>
<LUP006>Setup</LUP006>
<LUP007>Wireless Settings</LUP007>
<LUP008>IP Address Setup</LUP008>
<LUP009>Maintenance</LUP009>
<LUP010>Device Status</LUP010>
<LUP011>Backup Settings</LUP011>
<LUP012>Set Password</LUP012>
<LUP013>Advanced</LUP013>
<LUP014>Web Support</LUP014>
<LUP015>Knowledge Base</LUP015>
<LUP016>Documentation</LUP016>
<LUP017>Logout</LUP017>
<LUP018>Please select your preferred language</LUP018>
<LUP019>Setup Wizard</LUP019>
<WP0001>Thank you for purchasing NETGEAR's </WP0001>
<WP0002>Be sure to use the Firmware Upgrade Assistant periodically to take advantage of improvements and feature additions NETGEAR offers for this product.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</WP0002>
<WP0003>To take advantage of the Wireless-N features offered by the</WP0003>
<WP0004>device, use a wireless router that displays this logo.</WP0004>
<WP0005>Do not display this message again.</WP0005>
<WP0006>Close Window</WP0006>
<WPS001>Add WPS Client</WPS001>
<WPS002>Connect to Wireless Network</WPS002>
<WPS003>Select a setup method</WPS003>
<WPS004>Push 'N' Connect (recommended)</WPS004>
<WPS005>You can either press the physical push button on the device or click the button (soft push button) in this screen.</WPS005>
<WPS006>PIN Number</WPS006>
<WPS007>This is client PIN which provides randomly-generated PIN number. Please write down below PIN number and enter it in AP's WPS PIN GUI to run WPS.</WPS007>
<WPS008>Please click the software or hardware button on the wireless AP/router to start the WPS process...</WPS008>
<WPS009>Success</WPS009>
<WPS010>You have successfully connected to wireless network:</WPS010>
<WPS011>Click &lt;b&gt;OK&lt;/b&gt; to go back to the Wi-Fi Protected Setup screen.</WPS011>
<WPS012>Failure</WPS012>
<WPS013>WPS procedure timed out.</WPS013>
<WPS014>Failed to join the wireless network in 2 minutes. Please try later.</WPS014>
<WPS015>&lt;B&gt;&lt;CENTER&gt;&lt;FONT COLOR=\"red\"&gt;WPS procedure was cancelled by user.&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/CENTER&gt;&lt;/B&gt;</WPS015>
<WPS016>Failed to join the wireless network.</WPS016>
<WPS017>&lt;B&gt;&lt;FONT COLOR=\"red\"&gt; Security Risk: detecting more than one AP with push button pressed. &lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/B&gt;</WPS017>
<WPS018>The client's PIN is</WPS018>
<WPS019>Please enter the PIN into AP's GUI to join the wireless network.</WPS019>
<WPS020>Next</WPS020>
<WPS022>Connecting to Wireless Network</WPS022>
<WPSH01>&lt;body bgcolor="#0099cc"&gt;&lt;h1&gt;Connect to wireless network Help&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;WPS stands for Wi-Fi Protected Setup. This is a process that let you connect to the wireless network easily, and you don't have to specificly configure the wireless settings like SSID, security mode, and passphrase.</WPSH01>
<WPSH02>&lt;p&gt;You can connect to wireless AP either through the "Push 'N' Connect" or "PIN Number".&lt;BR&gt;</WPSH02>
<WPSH03>&lt;p&gt;With the "Push 'N' Connect" method, you have to complete the process by clicking a button on the wireless AP/router (either a hardware button or a software button on the AP's GUI).</WPSH03>
<WPSH04>&lt;p&gt;With the "PIN Number" method, you have to write down the client's PIN and enter it in the AP's WPS PIN GUI. You have to start the AP WPS
process at the same time after you finish to enter PIN in AP's GUI, and you must also click Next to start WPS here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</WPSH04>
<SWS001>Wireless Settings</SWS001>
<SWS002>Wireless Network</SWS002>
<SWS003>Name (SSID)</SWS003>
<SWS004>Region</SWS004>
<SWS005>Africa</SWS005>
<SWS006>Asia</SWS006>
<SWS007>Australia</SWS007>
<SWS008>Canada</SWS008>
<SWS009>Europe</SWS009>
<SWS010>Israel</SWS010>
<SWS011>Japan</SWS011>
<SWS012>Korea</SWS012>
<SWS013>Middle East</SWS013>
<SWS014>Mexico</SWS014>
<SWS015>South America</SWS015>
<SWS016>United States</SWS016>
<SWS017>Mode</SWS017>
<SWS018>Up to 300 Mbps</SWS018>
<SWS019>Up to 270Mbps</SWS019>
<SWS020>Up to 145 Mbps</SWS020>
<SWS021>Up to 130Mbps</SWS021>
<SWS022>Up to 54 Mbps</SWS022>
<SWS023>Up to 150 Mbps</SWS023>
<SWS024>Up to 65 Mbps</SWS024>
<SWS025>b and g</SWS025>
<SWS026>g only</SWS026>
<SWS027>b only</SWS027>
<SWS028>Security Options</SWS028>
<SWS029>None</SWS029>
<SWS030>WEP</SWS030>
<SWS031>WPA-PSK [TKIP]</SWS031>
<SWS032>WPA2-PSK [AES]</SWS032>
<SWS033>Security Encryption (WEP)</SWS033>
<SWS034>Encryption Strength</SWS034>
<SWS035>64-bit</SWS035>
<SWS036>128-bit</SWS036>
<SWS037>Security Encryption (WEP) Key</SWS037>
<SWS038>Passphrase</SWS038>
<SWS039>Generate</SWS039>
<SWS040>Key 1</SWS040>
<SWS041>Key 2</SWS041>
<SWS042>Key 3</SWS042>
<SWS043>Key 4</SWS043>
<SWS044>(8-63 characters or 64 hex digits)</SWS044>
<SWS045>&lt;b&gt;Note:&lt;/b&gt; The passphrase is case sensitive. "Netgear" is not the same as "netgear".</SWS045>
<SWS046>Channel</SWS046>
<SWS047>Security Type</SWS047>
<SWS048>Signal Strength</SWS048>
<SWS049>Manually input my wireless SSID</SWS049>
<SWS050></SWS050>
<SWS051>Select Existing Network</SWS051>
<SWS052>Search</SWS052>
<SWS053>Scanning</SWS053>
<SWS054>Detecting the wireless network in your neighborhood. This typically takes 10 seconds.</SWS054>
<SWSW01>WARNING: Selecting the incorrect region may result in a violation of applicable law. Do you agree to act in accordance with these settings?</SWSW01>
<SWSW02>“This security type WPA-PSK [AES] or WPA2-PSK [TKIP] is not supported.”</SWSW02>
<SWSW03>IMPORTANT</SWSW03>
<SWSW04>WPA-PSK [TKIP] ONLY operates at "Up to 54Mbps" (legacy G) mode, not N mode.</SWSW04>
<SWSW05>NETGEAR recommends that you use WPA2-PSK [AES] to get full N rate support.</SWSW05>
<SWSE01>Character is not allowed in passphrase.</SWSE01>
<SWSE02>Character is not allowed in SSID.</SWSE02>
<SWSE03>Maximum key length is </SWSE03>
<SWSE04>The passphrase is too long. The maximum length is 63 characters.</SWSE04>
<SWSE05>Insufficient passphrase length. It should be a minimum of 8 characters long.</SWSE05>
<SWSE06>SSID cannot be blank.</SWSE06>
<SWSE07> characters.</SWSE07>
<SWSE08>Invalid Key.</SWSE08>
<SWSE09>Keys length should be 26 Hex (0~9 and A~F) chars.</SWSE09>
<SWSE10>Keys length should be 10 Hex (0~9 and A~F) chars.</SWSE10>
<SWSH01>&lt;body bgColor=#0099cc&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;font size=4&gt;&lt;B&gt;Wireless Help&lt;/B&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;B&gt;NOTE:&lt;/B&gt; To ensure proper agency compliance and compatibility between similar products in your area, the operating region must be set correctly. &lt;P&gt;&lt;B&gt;Placement of the Router to Optimize Wireless Connectivity&lt;/B&gt;&lt;P&gt;The operating distance or range of your wireless connection can vary significantly based on the physical placement of the router. For best results, place your router:&lt;UL&gt;&lt;LI&gt;Near the center of the area in which your PCs will operate.&lt;LI&gt;In an elevated location such as a high shelf.&lt;LI&gt;Away from potential sources of interference, such as PCs, microwave ovens, and cordless phones.&lt;LI&gt;Away from large metal surfaces. &lt;/LI&gt;&lt;/UL&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;B&gt;Note:&lt;/B&gt; Failure to follow these guidelines can result in significant performance degradation or inability to wirelessly connect to the router.&lt;/P&gt;</SWSH01>
<SWSH02>&lt;HR&gt;&lt;A name=network&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;B&gt;Wireless Network&lt;/B&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;Name (SSID)&lt;P&gt;Enter a value of up to 32 alphanumeric characters. The same name (SSID) must be assigned to all wireless devices in your network. The default SSID is NETGEAR, but NETGEAR strongly recommends that you change your network's name (SSID) to a different value. This value is case-sensitive. For example, NETGEAR is not the same as NETGEAr.&lt;P&gt;Region&lt;P&gt;Select your region from the drop-down list. This field displays the region of operation for which the wireless interface is intended. It might not be legal to operate the device in a region other than the region shown here. If your country or region is not listed, please check with your local government agency or check the NETGEAR website for more information about which channels to use.</SWSH02>
<SWSH03>&lt;P&gt;Mode&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;Select the wireless mode you want to use. The options are:&lt;/P&gt;&lt;UL&gt;&lt;LI&gt;Up to 54 Mbps. Legacy Mode, with a maximum speed of up to 54 Mbps for b/g networks.&lt;LI&gt;Up to 145 Mbps. Neighbor-Friendly Mode, with a speed of up to 145 Mbps in the presence of neighboring wireless networks.&lt;LI&gt;Up to 300 Mbps. Performance Mode, with a maximum Wireless-N speed of up to 300 Mbps.&lt;/LI&gt;&lt;/UL&gt;&lt;P&gt;The default is &lt;b&gt;Up to 300 Mbps&lt;/b&gt;, which allows all 11b and 11g and 11n wireless stations. &lt;/P&gt;</SWSH03>
<SWSH04>&lt;HR&gt;&lt;A name=security&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Security Options&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;UL&gt;&lt;LI&gt;None - no data encryption&lt;LI&gt;WEP - Wired Equivalent Privacy, use WEP 64- or 128-bit data encryption&lt;LI&gt;WPA-PSK [TKIP] - Wi-Fi Protected Access with Pre-Shared Key, use WPA-PSK standard encryption with TKIP encryption type&lt;LI&gt;WPA2-PSK [AES] - Wi-Fi Protected Access version 2 with Pre-Shared Key, use WPA2-PSK standard encryption with the AES encryption type&lt;/UL&gt;&lt;p&gt;To achieve the best performance with 11N wireless adapters under robust security network, NETGEAR recommends that you change your network's security option to WPA2-PSK.&lt;/p&gt;</SWSH04>
<SWSH05>&lt;HR&gt;&lt;A name=wep&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Security Encryption (WEP) &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Encryption Strength &lt;p&gt;Select the WEP Encryption level: &lt;UL&gt;&lt;LI&gt;64-bit (sometimes called 40-bit) encryption &lt;LI&gt;128-bit encryption &lt;/LI&gt;&lt;/UL&gt;</SWSH05>
<SWSH06>&lt;HR&gt;&lt;A name=wepkey&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Security Encryption (WEP) Key&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If WEP is enabled, you can manually or automatically program the four data encryption keys. These values must be identical on all PCs and Access Points in your network. &lt;p&gt;Automatic Key Generation (Passphrase) &lt;p&gt;Enter a word or group of printable characters in the Passphrase box and click the Generate button to automatically configure the WEP Key(s). If encryption strength is set to 64 bit, then each of the four key boxes will automatically be populated with key values. If encryption strength is set to 128 bit, then only the selected WEP key box will automatically be populated with key values. &lt;p&gt;Manual Entry Mode &lt;p&gt;Select which of the four keys will be used, and enter the matching WEP key information for your network in the selected key box. &lt;p&gt;For 64-bit WEP - Enter ten hexadecimal digits (any combination of 0-9, A-F). &lt;p&gt;For 128-bit WEP - Enter twenty-six hexadecimal digits (any combination of 0-9, A-F). &lt;p&gt;Be sure to click Apply to save your settings in this menu.&lt;/P&gt;</SWSH06>
<SWSH07>&lt;HR&gt;&lt;A name=wpa-psk&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Security Encryption (WPA-PSK)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If selected, you must use TKIP encryption, and enter the WPA passphrase (Network key). Enter a word or group of printable characters in the Passphrase box. The Passphrase must be constituted of either 8 to 63 ASCII characters or exactly 64 hex digits. A hex digit is one of the following characters: &lt;br&gt;0, 1, 2, ..., 8, 9, A, B, C, D, E, and F. &lt;p&gt;Be sure to click Apply to save your settings. &lt;/p&gt;</SWSH07>
<SWSH08>&lt;HR&gt;&lt;A name=wpa2-psk&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Security Encryption (WPA2-PSK)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;WPA2 is a newer version of WPA. Only select this if all the wireless clients in your network support WPA2. If selected, you must use AES encryption, and enter the WPA passphrase (Network key). Enter a word or group of printable characters in the Passphrase box. The Passphrase must be constituted of either 8 to 63 ASCII characters or exactly 64 hex digits. A hex digit is one of the following characters: &lt;br&gt;0, 1, 2, ..., 8, 9, A, B, C, D, E, and F. &lt;/p&gt;</SWSH08>
<SWSH09>&lt;HR&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;To Save Or Cancel Changes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Apply&lt;/b&gt; to have your changes take effect. &lt;br&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Cancel&lt;/b&gt; to return to the previous settings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</SWSH09>
<SIAS001>Device's IP Address</SIAS001>
<SIAS002>Get Dynamically From Router</SIAS002>
<SIAS003>Use Static IP Address</SIAS003>
<SIAS004>IP Address</SIAS004>
<SIAS005>IP Subnet Mask</SIAS005>
<SIAS006>Gateway IP Address</SIAS006>
<SIAS007>Primary DNS</SIAS007>
<SIAS008>Secondary DNS</SIAS008>
<SIASE01>Invalid IP address. Please enter it again.</SIASE01>
<SIASE02>Invalid subnet mask. Please enter it again.</SIASE02>
<SIASE03>Invalid gateway IP address. Please enter it again.</SIASE03>
<SIASE04>The IP address and gateway IP address must be in the same subnet.</SIASE04>
<SIASE05>Invalid primary DNS address. Please enter it again.</SIASE05>
<SIASE06>Invalid secondary DNS address. Please enter it again.</SIASE06>
<SIASH01>&lt;body bgColor=#0099cc&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;font size=4&gt;&lt;B&gt;Device's IP Address Setup Help&lt;/B&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;The IP address settings of this device.&lt;/P&gt;</SIASH01>
<SIASH02>&lt;P&gt;&lt;B&gt;Get Dynamically From Router:&lt;/B&gt; The dhcp client of device will get an IP address automatically after it connects to your existing router.&lt;/P&gt;</SIASH02>
<SIASH03>&lt;P&gt;&lt;B&gt;Use Static IP Address:&lt;/B&gt; Set static IP address and related information of your network for this device.&lt;/P&gt;</SIASH03>
<SIASH04>&lt;UL&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;B&gt;IP Address:&lt;/B&gt; Type the IP address of your device in dotted decimal notation.</SIASH04>
<SIASH05>&lt;li&gt;&lt;B&gt;IP Subnet Mask:&lt;/B&gt; The subnet mask specifies the network number portion of an IP address. The device will automatically calculate the subnet mask based on the IP address that you assign. Unless you are implementing subnetting, use 255.255.255.0 as the subnet mask (computed by the device).</SIASH05>
<SIASH06>&lt;li&gt;&lt;B&gt;Gateway IP Address:&lt;/B&gt; Type the IP address of your gateway in dotted decimal notation.</SIASH06>
<SIASH07>&lt;li&gt;&lt;B&gt;Primary DNS:&lt;/B&gt; Specify the primary DNS server you want to use.</SIASH07>
<SIASH08>&lt;li&gt;&lt;B&gt;Secondary DNS:&lt;/B&gt; Specify the secondary DNS server you want to use.&lt;/UL&gt;</SIASH08>
<SIASH09>&lt;HR&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;To Save Or Cancel Changes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Apply&lt;/b&gt; to have your changes take effect. &lt;br&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Cancel&lt;/b&gt; to return to the previous settings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</SIASH09>
<MDS001>Device Status</MDS001>
<MDS002>Hardware Version</MDS002>
<MDS003>Firmware Version</MDS003>
<MDS004>GUI Language Version</MDS004>
<MDS005>Connection Status</MDS005>
<MDS006>Wireless Connection</MDS006>
<MDS007>Connect</MDS007>
<MDS008>Disconnect</MDS008>
<MDS009>Link Rate (Tx/Rx)</MDS009>
<MDS010>LAN Port</MDS010>
<MDS011>MAC Address</MDS011>
<MDS012>IP Address</MDS012>
<MDS013>DHCP Server</MDS013>
<MDS014>Subnet Mask</MDS014>
<MDS015>Default Gateway</MDS015>
<MDS016>DNS Server</MDS016>
<MDS017>Wireless Port</MDS017>
<MDS018>Name (SSID)</MDS018>
<MDS019>Region</MDS019>
<MDS020>Mode</MDS020>
<MDS021>Show Statistics</MDS021>
<MDS022>System Up Time</MDS022>
<MDS023>Day</MDS023>
<MDS024>Days</MDS024>
<MDS025>Port</MDS025>
<MDS026>Status</MDS026>
<MDS027>TxPkts</MDS027>
<MDS028>RxPkts</MDS028>
<MDS029>Collisions</MDS029>
<MDS030>Tx B/s</MDS030>
<MDS031>Rx B/s</MDS031>
<MDS032>Up Time</MDS032>
<MDS033>LAN</MDS033>
<MDS034>Link Down</MDS034>
<MDS035>Full</MDS035>
<MDS036>Half</MDS036>
<MDS037>WLAN</MDS037>
<MDS038>Poll Interval</MDS038>
<MDS039>(secs)</MDS039>
<MDS040>Set Interval</MDS040>
<MDS041>Stop</MDS041>
<MDS042>DHCP Connection</MDS042>
<MDS043>DHCP Server</MDS043>
<MDS044>Lease Obtained</MDS044>
<MDS045>Lease Expires</MDS045>
<MDS046>Hours</MDS046>
<MDS047>Minutes</MDS047>
<MDS048>Seconds</MDS048>
<MDS049>Release</MDS049>
<MDS050>Renew</MDS050>
<MDS051>Close Window</MDS051>
<MDS052>Mbps</MDS052>
<MDS053>OFF</MDS053>
<MDS054>ON</MDS054>
<MDS055>54Mbps</MDS055>
<MDS056>130Mbps</MDS056>
<MDS057>145Mbps</MDS057>
<MDS058>300Mbps</MDS058>
<MDS059>N/A</MDS059>
<MDS060>Wireless Connection Status</MDS060>
<MDSH01>&lt;body bgcolor=#0099cc &gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;font size=4&gt;&lt;B&gt;Device Status Help&lt;/B&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/P&gt;    &lt;p&gt;You can use the Device Status screen to check the current settings and statistics for your device. This screen shows you the current settings. If something needs to be changed, you will have to change it on the relevant screen.</MDSH01>
<MDSH02>&lt;a name=hard&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hardware Version&lt;/b&gt;: This is the hardware version of this device.&lt;/p&gt;</MDSH02>
<MDSH03>&lt;a name=firv&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Firmware Version&lt;/b&gt;: This is the current software the device is using. This will change if you upgrade your device.</MDSH03>
<MDSH04>&lt;a name=gui_lang&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;GUI Language Version&lt;/b&gt;: This is the current language version the device GUI is using. This will change if you upgrade your device.</MDSH04>
<MDSH05>&lt;a name="wireless connection_status"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wireless Connection Status&lt;/b&gt;: These are the current wireless connection status.</MDSH05>
<MDSH06>&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wireless Connection - indicates the wireless conneciton is &lt;i&gt;Connect&lt;/i&gt; or &lt;i&gt;Disconnect&lt;/i&gt;.</MDSH06>
<MDSH07>&lt;li&gt;Link Rate (Tx/Rx) - indicates the actual transmission (Tx)and receive (Rx) link rate in the current wireless connection.</MDSH07>
<MDSH08>&lt;a name="lan_port"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;LAN Port&lt;/b&gt;: These are the current settings, as set in the &lt;i&gt;IP Address Setup&lt;/i&gt; page.</MDSH08>
<MDSH09>&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;MAC Address - the physical address of the Device, as seen from the local LAN.</MDSH09>
<MDSH10>&lt;li&gt;IP Address - LAN IP address of the Device.</MDSH10>
<MDSH11>&lt;li&gt;DHCP Client - indicates either &lt;i&gt;On&lt;/i&gt; (IP address is obtained dynamically) or &lt;i&gt;Off&lt;/i&gt;.</MDSH11>
<MDSH12>&lt;li&gt;Subnet Mask - subnet mask associated with the LAN IP address.</MDSH12>
<MDSH13>&lt;li&gt;Default Gateway - displays the IP address of default gateway.</MDSH13>
<MDSH14>&lt;li&gt;DNS Server - displays the IP address of the current DNS (Domain Name Server).&lt;/ul&gt;</MDSH14>
<MDSH15>&lt;a name="wireless_port"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wireless Port&lt;/b&gt;: These are the current settings, as set in the &lt;i&gt;Wireless Settings&lt;/i&gt; page.</MDSH15>
<MDSH16>&lt;li&gt;Name (SSID) - SSID of the Router.</MDSH16>
<MDSH17>&lt;li&gt;Region - the location (country).</MDSH17>
<MDSH18>&lt;li&gt;Channel - the current channel in use.</MDSH18>
<MDSH19>&lt;li&gt;Mode - indicates the current wireless mode.</MDSH19>
<MDSH20>&lt;li&gt;Security type - indicates the security type used in the wireless network.&lt;/ul&gt;</MDSH20>
<MDSH21>&lt;p&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Show Statistics&lt;/b&gt; to see device performance statistics such as the number of packets sent and number of packets received for each port.</MDSH21>
<MDSH22>&lt;p&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;DHCP Status&lt;/b&gt; to see information about your current DHCP connection.&lt;/p&gt;</MDSH22>
<MBS001>Backup Settings</MBS001>
<MBS002>Save a copy of current settings</MBS002>
<MBS003>Back Up</MBS003>
<MBS004>Restore saved settings from a file</MBS004>
<MBS005>Restore</MBS005>
<MBS006>Revert to factory default settings</MBS006>
<MBS007>Erase</MBS007>
<MBS008>Loading the factory default settings will erase all the current settings.</MBS008>
<MBS009>Are you sure you want to do this?</MBS009>
<MBS010>Yes</MBS010>
<MBS011>No</MBS011>
<MBSW01>Warning!</MBSW01>
<MBSW02>Restoring settings from a configuration file will erase all of the current settings. </MBSW02>
<MBSW03>Are you sure you want to do this?</MBSW03>
<MBSW04>Please select correct configuration file.</MBSW04>
<MBSW05>Please assign the correct file. (File format is *.cfg.)</MBSW05>
<MBSE01>Filename can not be blank.</MBSE01>
<MBSH01>&lt;body bgcolor=#0099cc &gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;font size=4&gt;&lt;b&gt;Backup Settings Help&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This screen allows you to back up, restore, and erase the device's current settings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once you have the device working correctly, you should back up the information to have it available if something goes wrong. When you back up the settings, they are saved as a file on your computer. You can restore the device's settings from this file. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a name=save&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;To create a backup file of the current settings:&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Back Up&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If you do not have your browser set up to save downloaded files automatically, locate where you want to save the file, rename it if you like, and click &lt;b&gt;Save&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;br&gt;If you have your browser set up to save downloaded files automatically, the file is saved to the your browser's download location on the hard disk and is called </MBSH01>
<MBSH02>. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;IMPORTANT!&lt;/b&gt;Once you start restoring settings or erasing the device, do &lt;I&gt;not&lt;/I&gt; try to go online, turn off the device, shut down the computer, or do anything else to the device until it finishes restarting! This should take only a minute or so. When the Test light stops blinking, wait a few more seconds before doing anything with the device. &lt;/p&gt;</MBSH02>
<MBSH03>&lt;hr&gt;&lt;a name=restore&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;To restore settings from a backup file:&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Browse&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locate and select the previously saved backup file (by default, </MBSH03>
<MBSH04>).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Restore&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;br&gt;A window appears letting you know that the device has been successfully restored to the previous settings. The device will restart. This will take about 1 minute.&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;IMPORTANT!&lt;/b&gt;Do not try to go online, turn off the device, shut down the computer, or do anything else to the device until it finishes restarting! When the Test light stops blinking, wait a few more seconds before doing anything with the device. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Close the message window.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;a name=revert&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;To erase the current settings and reset the device to the original factory default settings:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Erase&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;IMPORTANT!&lt;/b&gt;Do not try to go online, turn off the device, shut down the computer, or do anything else to the device until the device finishes restarting! When the Test light stops blinking, wait a few more seconds before doing anything with the device. &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;After you have erased the device's current settings, the device's password will be &lt;b&gt;password&lt;/b&gt;, the LAN IP address will be &lt;b&gt;192.168.1.1&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</MBSH04>
<MSP001>Password</MSP001>
<MSP002>Old Password</MSP002>
<MSP003>Set Password</MSP003>
<MSP004>Repeat New Password</MSP004>
<MSPE01>Maximum password length is 32 characters!</MSPE01>
<MSPE02>The password you typed does not match. Please enter it again.</MSPE02>
<MSPE03>The old password is wrong!</MSPE03>
<MSPH01>&lt;body bgcolor=#0099cc &gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;font size=4&gt;&lt;B&gt;Set Password Help&lt;/B&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;p&gt; You use the Set Password screen to change the password you use to access the Settings screens,&lt;I&gt;not&lt;/I&gt; your ISP account password. &lt;p&gt; To change the password: &lt;ol&gt; &lt;li&gt;Type the old password.   &lt;BR&gt;The default password for the device is &lt;b&gt;password&lt;/b&gt;.  &lt;li&gt;Type a new password, and type it again in the &lt;b&gt;Repeat New Password&lt;/b&gt; field to confirm it.   &lt;br&gt;  &lt;b&gt;Note:&lt;/B&gt; Be sure to write it down in a secure location.  &lt;li&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Apply&lt;/b&gt; to change the password, or click &lt;b&gt;Cancel&lt;/b&gt; to keep the current password. &lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;b&gt;Note:&lt;/b&gt; If you have backed up the device settings previously, you should do a new backup so that the settings file includes the new password. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</MSPH01>
<MFU001>Checking for Firmware Updates</MFU001>
<MFU002>The device is checking the NETGEAR server to see if updated firmware available for your device. &lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt; This could take up to </MFU002>
<MFU003> seconds, please wait ...</MFU003>
<MFU004>Check for new version upon login</MFU004>
<MFU005>Cancel</MFU005>
<MFU006>No Internet connection</MFU006>
<MFU007>No Internet connection is detected. The device cannot check the NETGEAR server for updated firmware. After setting up your Internet connection, go to the Firmware Upgrade screen to check for updated firmware.</MFU007>
<MFU008>OK</MFU008>
<MFU009>Firmware Version Check</MFU009>
<MFU010>No new firmware version available.</MFU010>
<MFU011>This screen will automatically return to the previous screen in a few seconds...</MFU011>
<MFU012>Firmware Upgrade Assistant</MFU012>
<MFU013>Firmware Upgrade</MFU013>
<MFU014>A new version has been found. Do You want to upgrade to the new version now?</MFU014>
<MFU015>Current Firmware Version</MFU015>
<MFU016>New Firmware Version</MFU016>
<MFU017>Check</MFU017>
<MFU018>Locate and select the upgrade file on your hard disk.</MFU018>
<MFU019>Upload</MFU019>
<MFU020>Warning! The firmware version you are trying to upload is older than the one you had.</MFU020>
<MFU021>Current Version</MFU021>
<MFU022>Uploaded Version</MFU022>
<MFU023>&lt;b&gt;Note:&lt;/b&gt;It will take about </MFU023>
<MFU024> minutes for firmware upgrade.&lt;br&gt;Please don't turn off the power or press reset button.</MFU024>
<MFU025>Current GUI Language Version</MFU025>
<MFU026>New GUI Language Version</MFU026>
<MFU027>Release Notes</MFU027>
<MFU028>Warning! You are trying to download firmware with version V</MFU028>
<MFU029> is older than the firmware with version V</MFU029>
<MFU030>you had. Do you want to continue?</MFU030>
<MFU031>Warning! You are trying to upload </MFU031>
<MFU032>which is different from the </MFU032>
<MFU033>you had.</MFU033>
<MFU034></MFU034>
<MFU035>a world wide firmware</MFU035>
<MFU036>a non world wide firmware</MFU036>
<MFU037>Check for New Version from the Internet</MFU037>
<MFUW01>The firmware upgrade can contain valuable enhancements.</MFUW01>
<MFUW02>Are you sure you want to turn off automatic checking?</MFUW02>
<MFUW03>After you turn it off, you can reenable it through the Firmware Upgrade screen.</MFUW03>
<MFUW04>Warning! You are trying to download the firmware which the region is different from the current firmware you had.</MFUW04>
<MFUW05>Do you want to switch from %s (the current language) to %s</MFUW05>
<MFUE01>The file name is null. Locate and select the upgrade file from your hard disk, please.</MFUE01>
<MFUE02>Memory allocation failed. Suggest re-upgrade after reboot or revert to factory default settings.</MFUE02>
<MFUE03>No Internet Connection Available</MFUE03>
<MFUE04>No new firmware version available.</MFUE04>
<MFUE05>Not enough memory for firmware upgrade</MFUE05>
<MFUE06>Not enough memory for GUI language upgrade</MFUE06>
<MFUE07>Not enough memory to perform version check</MFUE07>
<MFUE08>Firmware could not be downloaded from the NETGEAR server. Please check your Internet connection.</MFUE08>
<MFUE09>Unable to download GUI language file from Netgear server</MFUE09>
<MFUE10>Unable to get latest version information</MFUE10>
<MFUE11>Firmware is invalid</MFUE11>
<MFUE12>GUI language file is invalid</MFUE12>
<MFUE13>Firmware unavailable</MFUE13>
<MFUE14>GUI language file unavailable</MFUE14>
<MFUE15>Firmware upgrade failed. Please check your file.</MFUE15>
<MFUE16>Cannot connect to Netgear server</MFUE16>
<MFUE17>Failed to update Firmware</MFUE17>
<MFUE18>Failed to update GUI language file</MFUE18>
<MFUE19>Fail to login to Netgear server</MFUE19>
<MFUE20>Please assign the correct file. The file format is *.</MFUE20>
<MFUE21>Time out, file not found!!</MFUE21>
<MFUE23>Please wait for updating the GUI language…</MFUE23>
<MFUE24>Do you want to upgrade?</MFUE24>
<MFUE25>The device is downloading the new language pack now. Please Wait...</MFUE25>
<MFUE26>The device is downloading the new firmware now. Please Wait...</MFUE26>
<MFUE27>Do you really want to reprogram the device using the firmware file "%s"?</MFUE27>
<MFUE30>Do you really want to reprogram the device using the language package "%s"?</MFUE30>
<MFUH01>&lt;body bgcolor=#0099cc&gt;	&lt;P&gt;&lt;font size=4&gt;&lt;B&gt;Firmware Upgrade Assistant Help&lt;/B&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/P&gt;        &lt;p&gt;The device can automatically detect whether a new version of the firmware is available on the Internet.&lt;p&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Yes&lt;/b&gt; if you want to start the detection now.&lt;br&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;No&lt;/b&gt; if you want do not want to check for a new version now.&lt;p&gt;If you prefer to check for a new version later, you can do this on the Firmware Upgrade screen.&lt;p&gt;If you do not want to see this message again the next time you log in, select the &lt;b&gt;Do not display this message again&lt;/b&gt; check box, and click &lt;b&gt;No&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/body&gt;</MFUH01>
<MFUH02>&lt;body bgcolor=#0099cc &gt;&lt;h1&gt;Firmware Upgrade Help&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;You install new versions of the device's software using the &lt;i&gt;Firmware Upgrade&lt;/i&gt; page. &lt;p&gt;Go to the NETGEAR Web site to get new versions of the device software. After downloading the file, you'll need to unzip (or unstuff) it before upgrading the device.&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;IMPORTANT!&lt;/b&gt; Once you click &lt;b&gt;Upload&lt;/b&gt; do NOT interrupt the process of sending the software to the device and restarting the device. If you think the process may be interrupted in some way, click &lt;b&gt;Cancel&lt;/b&gt; to keep the current device software.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a name=locate&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;To upgrade device software:&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Go to www.NETGEAR.com and download the updated software.&lt;li&gt;If not done automatically, uncompress the file.&lt;br&gt;You may want to read the &lt;i&gt;Release Notes&lt;/i&gt; before continuing.&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Browse&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;li&gt;Locate and select the file you just downloaded and uncompressed.&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Upload&lt;/b&gt; to send the software to the device.&lt;br&gt;This loads the new software in the device and causes the device to restart.&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Note:&lt;/b&gt; Do not try to go online, turn off the device, shutdown the computer or do anything else to the device until the device finishes restarting! When the Ready light stops blinking, wait a few more seconds before doing anything.&lt;li&gt;Click &lt;b&gt;Status&lt;/b&gt; and check the Firmware Version to verify that your device now has the new software installed. &lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;B&gt;IMPORTANT!&lt;/b&gt; In some cases, such as a major upgrades, you may need to reconfigure your device after upgrading it. Refer to the &lt;i&gt;Release Notes&lt;/i&gt; included with the software to find out if you need to reconfigure the device. &lt;/body&gt;</MFUH02>
<AWS001>Advanced Wireless Settings</AWS001>
<AWS002>Fragmentation Length (256-2346)</AWS002>
<AWS003>CTS/RTS Threshold (1-2347)</AWS003>
<AWS004>Preamble Mode</AWS004>
<AWS005>Long Preamble</AWS005>
<AWS006>Short Preamble</AWS006>
<AWSE01>Fragmentation Length value is outside the range 256-2346.</AWSE01>
<AWSE02>CTS/RTS Threshold value is outside the range 1-2347.</AWSE02>
<AWSH01>&lt;body bgColor=#0099cc&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;font size=4&gt;&lt;B&gt;Advanced Wireless Help&lt;/B&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;B&gt;Warning: &lt;/B&gt;The device is already configured with the optimum settings. Do not alter these settings unless directed by NETGEAR support. Incorrect settings might disable the device unexpectedly.&lt;P&gt;Fragmentation Threshold, CTS/RTS Threshold, Preamble Mode&lt;P&gt;These settings are reserved for wireless testing and advanced configuration only. Do not change these settings.&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;B&gt;To Save or Cancel Changes&lt;/B&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;Click &lt;B&gt;Apply&lt;/B&gt; to have your changes take effect. &lt;BR&gt;Click &lt;B&gt;Cancel&lt;/B&gt; to return to the previous settings. &lt;/P&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</AWSH01>
<LGT001>Goodbye</LGT001>
<LGT002>Logout</LGT002>
<LGT003>Thank you for using the NETGEAR Web-based Configuration Utility.</LGT003>
<OTH001>No</OTH001>
<OTH002>Important Update</OTH002>
<OTH003>Checking JavaScript Support</OTH003>
<OTH004>To provide an enhanced user interface, this device uses JavaScript extensively.</OTH004>
<OTH005>If this page is not quickly replaced, your Browser does NOT support JavaScript.</OTH005>
<OTH006>Please enable JavaScript in your Browser, or use a different Browser.</OTH006>
<OTH007>http://kbserver.netgear.com/main.asp</OTH007>
<OTH008>Updating Settings</OTH008>
<OTHE01>Failure</OTHE01>
<OTHE02>Unknown Error: </OTHE02>
<OTHE03>400 Bad Request</OTHE03>
<OTHE04>This server does not support the operation requested by your client.</OTHE04>
<OTHE05>401 Unauthorized</OTHE05>
<OTHE06>Access to this resource is denied, your client has not supplied the correct authentication.</OTHE06>
<OTHE07>404 Not Found</OTHE07>
<OTHE08>Please upgrade to a version 4 or later browser so that you can use this setup tool (and see lots of great sites on the Internet).</OTHE08>
<OTHE09>is managing this device.</OTHE09>
<OTHE10>Please contact your system administrator for the correct information.</OTHE10>
<OTHE11>System authentication failed.</OTHE11>
<OTHE12>Warning</OTHE12>
<CA001>1-Select Existing Network</CA001>
<CA002>2-Apply Security</CA002>
<CA003>3-Connect to Existing Network</CA003>
<CA004>4-Review Settings</CA004>
<CA005>Congratulation! You have now successfully powered on </CA005>
<CA006>.  Next you will need to connect it to an existing wireless network.</CA006>
<CA007>Would you like help with that?</CA007>
<CA008>Yes.  Please guide me through the options. </CA008>
<CA009>No, I am an advanced user, and I can manually set up the connections. </CA009>
<CA010>Continue</CA010>
<CA011>Smart Wizard is detecting the wireless networks in your neighborhood. &lt;br&gt;This typically takes 10 seconds.</CA011>
<CA012>Please select the name of your existing network.</CA012>
<CA013>Refresh</CA013>
<CA014>Please enter the security passphrase associated with your existing network</CA014>
<CA015>&lt; Back</CA015>
<CA016>Please enter the security passphrase or WEP hex key associated with your existing network</CA016>
<CA017>Smart Wizard is connecting %s to the existing network.&lt;br&gt;This typically takes 1 minutes.</CA017>
<CA018>You have successfully connected to wireless network: </CA018>
<CA019>This is your wireless setting:</CA019>
<CA020>To manage advanced settings, please enter </CA020>
<CA021> in any browser such as Internet Explorer.</CA021>
<CA022>%s is having difficulty to connect to the selected network.</CA022>
<CA023>&lt;ul&gt;The possible cause is:</CA023>
<CA024>&lt;li&gt;The passphrase or WEP key entered does not match to the selected network.  Please make sure you enter the correct password.  Click "Try Again" to re-enter it.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</CA024>
<CA025>&lt;li&gt;Connection was not established to the selected network. Please see Question 3 in the FAQ section on the back of the Installation Guide for help.</CA025>
<CA026>Once you’re ready, click "Try Again" to attempt the connection again or "Cancel" to select a different network.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</CA026>
<CA027>You may close the browser window now.</CA027>
<CA028>Click "Finish" to exit the installation.</CA028>
<CA029>Finish</CA029>
<CA030>Try Again</CA030>
<CA031>Configuration</CA031>
<CA032>Connection was not established to the selected network.  Please move WNCE2001 closer to the selected network router.  When ready, click "Try Again.</CA032>
</root>